at Liberty General Insurance we care
about the convenience of our garage
officials as much as we care for our
customers that's why we have developed
an online motor claims registration
process which is quick and hassle-free
to register claims on our garage portal
or Liberty General Insurance website
follow these easy steps log to the
Liberty General Insurance garage portal
using your ID and password if you face
any login related issues then please
reach out to our claim officer for
assistance from the available options on
the screen select claim intimation after
entering the customer policy click on
search and you will be able to view all
the relevant details on the screen now
fill in all the accident related details
and click on register claim that's it in
just a few seconds the claim number will
be generated on the screen and will also
be shared Via SMS on the phone number
provided by you and the customer if you
prefer registering a claim through the
Liberty General Insurance website then
that is quite simple as well visit the
garage claims registration page on the
Liberty General Insurance website by
entering the customer policy number and
clicking on the search option you will
be able to view all the relevant
customer details now enter customer
contact details such as email ID and
phone number to register the claim fill
in all the details regarding the
accident and submit note down the claim
number that appears on the screen it
will also be shared via SMS on the phone
number provided by you and the customer
so you see without having to wait in
Long ibr cues you can now register
unlimited claims easily as per your
convenience
oh